<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">RecyclerView</string>
    <string name="news_content">
        EXTERNAL AFFAIRS Minister S Jaishankar on Wednesday held wide-ranging talks with his Russian counterpart Sergey Lavrov focusing on the Ukraine conflict, bilateral ties and issues relating to the G20 foreign ministers’ meeting. The Russian Foreign Minister landed in Delhi Tuesday night to attend a two-day meeting of the G20 foreign ministers that is taking place amid Russia’s escalating confrontation with the Western powers over the Ukraine conflict. “A wide ranging discussion with FM Sergey Lavrov of Russia on #G20FMM sidelines. Exchanged views on our bilateral cooperation and G20 issues,” Jaishankar tweeted. It is learnt that the Ukraine conflict figured in the talks.

        A Russian readout said the two ministers resolved to enhance coordination on the international stage and in multilateral forums including at the UN, G20, Shanghai Cooperation Organisation (SCO) and BRICS (Brazil-Russia-India-China-South Africa.

        They confirmed their compliance with the establishment of a polycentric world order based on fair and democratic principles and the rule of law,” it said.

        They confirmed their compliance with the establishment of a polycentric world order based on fair and democratic principles and the rule of law,” it said.
        However, confirmed their compliance with the establishment of a polycentric world order based on fair and democratic principles and the rule of law,” it said.

        The sides exchanged views in a confidential spirit on topical issues of the Russian-Indian relations, reaffirmed their focus on further strengthening the special and privileged strategic partnership in all areas.”</string>

    <string name="news_watch" tools:ignore="StringEscaping">
        See why this new smartwatch is gaining popularity in India and selling out everywhere.
        For a long time, the smartwatch industry had just a few big companies that could set any prices they wanted and kept ripping off customers. But now one tech startup is turning the $45 billion smartwatch industry on its head.

The company called GenFit Watch has figured out a way to offer a far superior product (even the biggest tech geeks agree) at a fraction of the price.

What Is It?
Meet the GenFit Watch.

The Japanese company behind the GenFit Watch are experts in health tech. Their engineers combined forces with some of the top watch makers in the world to develop the GenFit Watch.

GenFit Watch combines the benefits of a fitness band, digital watch, health monitor, and a handsfree headset all into one.

It feels comfortable on your wrist. Even better than some of the luxury smartwatches I own from other big tech companies.

Extreme workouts and outdoor sports? No problem, the hardened aluminum shell and tempered touchscreen glass wont scratch or break even if you tried.

In my opinion the GenFit Watch is the next generation of smartwatches.


Take calls, step counter, sleep monitoring, show incoming messages, etc The watch has all the basic functions that a good smartwatch must have and much more.

But what makes the GenFit Watch special are its features that could potentially give you a lot of health insights.... And what is that worth to you?

What Makes The GenFit Watch So Popular?
        The green laser behind the watch is the secret!

It is the heart rate monitoring function.

This watch lets you measure your blood pressure, heart rate - calculate your beats per minute (BPM). All in real-time.

It is capable of performing an Heart Rate test on you!

What Else Can The GenFit Watch Do?
More than you might suspect!.

        When looking at reviews there are a few features that stand out as the reason thousands of users give this watch 5-star reviews:


✅ Large Color 1.3" Display -HD clear, easy-to-read display, oversized for easy touch control.
✅ Step counter -Set goals, hit them and lose weight fast.
✅ Sleep Monitoring - Measures the physiological signals of your body, understand your lifestyle
✅ Calorie Monitoring -Incredibly useful if you are trying to lose, maintain or even gain weight
✅ Alarm Reminder -You will never forget your anniversary—or your dentist appointment again
✅ Incoming calls and notifications -Keep your phone safe in your pocket and use your watch to answer calls.
✅ State-of-the-art Fitness tracking -Record your workouts and get fit
✅ Long Standby -Long life battery, super-efficient, less annoying recharges
✅ Sedentary Warning -Tells you when to sit less and move more
✅ Great Styling -Premium looking smartwatch.
✅ Anti-lost -Call your lost phone from your GenFit Watch to find it fast
✅ Take a photo -Use your GenFit Watch to take a photo on your smartphone
✅ Sync to both iPhone and Android -Supports IOS and Andriod
✅ Control your music -The easiest way to change track and volume
and there is even more

    </string>
    <string name="news_rahul">
        In a relief for Congress leader Rahul Gandhi, a Surat sessions court on Monday granted bail, till disposal of his appeal, in the defamation case over his remark "why all thieves share the Modi surname" and also issued notice to the complainant on Gandhi`s plea for a stay on his conviction. According to legal experts, a stay on Gandhi’s conviction in the case would be sufficient to restore his Lok Sabha membership.
        Speaking to IANS, senior advocate Sanjay Hedge said according to the Supreme Court judgement in the Lily Thomas case, a stay on the conviction is sufficient and if the sessions court stays Rahul`s conviction, then the Lok Sabha secretariat could restore Gandhi`s membership. The sessions court will hear Gandhi’s appeal against conviction in the case on April 13.

Gandhi, the former President of Congress, arrived in Surat to file the appeal in sessions court against a lower court`s order that found him guilty of criminal defamation. The charges stemmed from a remark he made in April 2019 while campaigning for the Lok Sabha elections in Karnataka`s Kolar.

Senior advocate Sidharth Luthra said if the sessions court stays his conviction in the defamation case, it will pave the way for the restoration of his Lok Sabha membership. He stressed that a stay on conviction is a must.

A senior advocate, on the condition of anonymity, said Gandhi`s conviction has not been stayed by the court on Monday, however, a notice has been issued to the complainant on Gandhi`s plea seeking a stay on his conviction and the matter is scheduled for hearing on April 13. He added once his conviction is stayed, then the Lok Sabha secretariat can restore his membership.

During his campaign, Gandhi stated that "all thieves have Modi surname", equating Prime Minister Narendra Modi with fugitives like Lalit Modi and Nirav Modi. On March 23, a lower court in Surat found him guilty of defaming the entire Modi community in a case filed by BJP MLA Purnesh Modi. Gandhi was subsequently disqualified from the Lok Sabha under a rule that bars convicted MPs from holding Lok Sabha membership.

Gandhi was given the maximum 2-year jail term for his offence, but the sentence was suspended for 30 days for him to file an appeal against the order. If the conviction is not overturned, he will be disqualified from contesting elections for the next eight years.
    </string>
    <string name="news_Setu">
        The Bhupen Hazarika Setu, also known as Dhola-Sadiya Bridge is the longest bridge in India with a length of 9.15 km. The biggest road bridge of India is built on the Lohit River in the Tinsukia district of the state of Assam, and connects Assam with Arunachal Pradesh. Inaugurated by Prime Minister Narendra Modi on May 26, 2017, the bridge is an engineering marvel and a testimony to the progress India has made in road infrastructure under Nitin Gadkari, Union Minister of Road Transport and Highways ministry. Recently, Arunachal Pradesh CM Pema Khandu shared a breathtaking aerial view of the bridge.
        Sharing on Twitter, Pema Khandu wrote, "Bhupen Hazarika Setu ~ An engineering marvel, which has brought Arunachal and Assam closer! A testimony to Hon PM Shri @narendramodi Ji's commitment to develop Northeast. Watch The Panoramic Aerial View of India's Bridge Over Water!" The videos show a section of the bridge passing over the Lohit River, with poetry in the background.

    </string>
    <string name="news_ai">
        Advanced AI could represent a profound change in the history of life on Earth, and should be planned for and managed with commensurate care and resources," said the letter. "Unfortunately, this level of planning and management is not happening, even though recent months have seen AI labs locked in an out-of-control race to develop and deploy ever more powerful digital minds that no one – not even their creators – can understand, predict, or reliably control."

Companies like OpenAI, Microsoft, and Google have been charging full speed ahead with their generative AI models. Fueled by ambitions to corner the AI market, new advancements and product releases are announced on an almost daily basis. But the letter says it's all happening too fast for ethical, regulatory, and safety concerns to be considered.
        "We must ask ourselves: Should we let machines flood our information channels with propaganda and untruth? Should we automate away all the jobs, including the fulfilling ones? Should we develop nonhuman minds that might eventually outnumber, outsmart, obsolete and replace us? Should we risk loss of control of our civilization?"


    </string>
    <string name="news_deo">
        The pandemic has created strong tailwinds for global technology adoption at an unprecedented rate and accelerated the next wave of a smart urban transformation. Over the past challenging years, smart city innovations have emerged as the champion force to power the speedy recovery for economies and communities, reinventing a smarter future for all.


Being an international innovation and technology hub with the distinctive edge of global vision and strategic connectivity with the Greater Bay Area and the rest of the world, Hong Kong is set to spur new growth leveraging opportunities brought by the National 14th Five-Year Plan and from the new opportunities worldwide. The upcoming DES (rebranded from the Internet Economy Summit, IES) will unveil global and regional visions on how smart city technologies will supercharge smart economies as well as accelerate the formation of futureproof digital societies.

    </string>
    <string name="news_war">
        Ukraine will launch an international campaign to prevent Russian athletes from competing in the Paris 2024 Olympic Games, President Zelenskyy said.

“Today we will a start a marathon for fair play aimed at clearing the management of international Olympic structures of hypocrisy as well as [preventing] any attempts to drag representatives of the terrorist state into world sport,” Zelenskyy said in a video address.

“It is obvious that any neutral flag of Russian athletes would be stained with blood … Olympic principles and war are fundamentally opposed to each other.”

Sport minister Vadim Guttsait earlier said Ukraine would not rule out boycotting the Games if Russian and Belarusian athletes took part. They have been banned in some sports while they are allowed to compete under a neutral flag in others.

Russian foreign ministry spokeswoman Maria Zakharova said any attempt to squeeze Moscow out of international sport was “doomed to fail”.
        A total of 321 heavy tanks have been promised to Ukraine by several countries, according to Ukraine’s ambassador to France.

“As of today, numerous countries have officially confirmed their agreement to deliver 321 heavy tanks to Ukraine,” Ambassador Vadym Omelchenko said in an interview with French TV station BFM.

“Delivery terms vary for each case and we need this help as soon as possible,” he added.

Omelchenko did not provide a breakdown of the number of tanks per country.

Several Western nations led by Germany and the United States said they would send tanks to Ukraine.


    </string>

</resources>